Guide to the Administrative Papers of the President George Bugliarello RG.006
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series II: Bern Dibner Library / CATT
  - Engineering, 1988 August-1992 December (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Program Investigation for Center for Advanced Technology in Telecommunications, 1987 January (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Program – Library, 1987 October-1992 March (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Program – Library, 1985 October-1991 January (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - A Proposal to Provide Preconstruction and Construction Management Services, 1987 February 6 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Statement of Credentials, 1987 January 28 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Program – CATT, 1988 June-1992 April (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Program – CATT, 1985 March-1988 June (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Operation & Management, 1986 July-1992 July (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Utilities, 1989 April-1992 October (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Flood Damage & Claim, 1991 August-1993 July (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Consultant Agreement, 1989 July-March (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Additional Building Items, 1991 October-1994 April (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Library / CATT Building Owner's Costs, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Morse Diesel, 1991 May-1992 April (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Morse Diesel, 1992 May-1993 February (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Farmingdale Septic Tank, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Farmingdale Loan Agreement, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Poly Dorm Bonds of 1962 – Master (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Request for Dorm Loan from Housing & Home Finance Agency, 1962 October-November (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Building - Building Signage, 1991 October (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Morse Diesel Monthly Job Progress, 1990 July-September (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Morse Diesel Monthly Job Progress, 1990 May-June (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Polytechnic Library Building Program Draft, 1984 August 30 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Farmingdale Housing, 1989 May-1990 February (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Long Island Campus Pre-Fab, 1988 April-1990 January (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - L.I.C. Mortgage Equipment & Furnishings Industry, 1985 June-1989 February (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Farmingdale Campus - Space Electronics Institute, 1988 February-June (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Long Island Architects, 1988 February-April (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Farmingdale Campus Survey Prepared by Bohn & Bonacci, 1987 October-1989 August (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Steven J. Hyman Association Engineering Drawings & Blue Prints, 1982, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Record of Invoices L.I.C. (Long Island Campus) Dorm Project, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - L.I.C. Dorm Project 1989-1991, Owner (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - L.I.C. Dorm Project, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Reports – Construction Meetings – 1962-1963, 1962 December-1963 November (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Proposal to U.S. Office of Education, L.I.C., 1965 March 29 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Farmingdale Construction Bids, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Antennae Range – L.I.C., 1963 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence – L.I.C. – 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Cullen & Dykman – L.I.C., 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Payroll Records – L.I.C., 1963 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Insurance Certificates – L.I.C., 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Housings & Home Finance Agency, 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Dormitory – L.I.C., 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Publicity – L.I.C., 1963 January-February (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Punch List – L.I.C., 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Physical Planning Bulleting – L.I.C., 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Sketches – Photographs – L.I.C., 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Bills – L.I.C. Construction Account, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Eggers & Higgins – L.I.C., 1959-1965 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Survey – L.I.C., 1962 December-1963 January (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Approvals – L.I.C., 1962 December-1963 July (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Contract Payments – Ross Wein Inc. – L.I.C., 1962 August-1966 June (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Ross-Wein Inc. – L.I.C., 1962 December-1965 March (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Schedules – L.I.C., 1963 January 2 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Sykes, Galloway & Dykman (Attorneys) – L.I.C., 1963 January-1964 January (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Construction Management – Dibner / CATT, 1991 February-December (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Construction Management – Dibner / CATT, 1987 May-1991 February (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Library / CATT Architects Fee, 1990 January-1992 November (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Library / CATT Architects Fee, 1986 October-1989 December (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Library / CATT building – Owner's Costs II – Additional / Professional Services – 6A-6C, 1988-1992 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Library / CATT building – Owner's Costs II – Additional / Professional Services – 6D-6F, 1988-1992 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Library / CATT building – Owner's Costs II – Additional / Professional Services – 6G, 1988-1992 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Library / CATT building – Owner's Costs II – Additional / Professional Services – 6H – Others – 1 – 5, 1988-1992 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Library / CATT building – Owner's Costs II – Additional / Professional Services – 6H – 6-14, 1988-1992 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Library / CATT building – Owner's Costs II – Additional / Professional Services – 6H (15), 7, 1988-1992 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Library / CATT Trade Awards, 1988-1992 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Library / CATT Trade Awards, 1988-1992 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Morse Diesel – Final Working Drawing Budget, 1989 July, 1990 September (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Morse Diesel – Design/ Development Budget Cost Savings / Value Engineering, 1989 July 28 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1991 July (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1991 June (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1991 May (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1991 March-April (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1991 February (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1991 January (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1990 December (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1990 November (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1990 October (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1990 September (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Morse Diesel – Monthly Construction Report, 1990 August (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Building Telecommunications Invoices, 1989 February-1992 September (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Dibner / CATT – Construction Bulletin, 1990 June-1991 April (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Dibner / CATT – Punch Cards, 1992 January-May (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Dibner / CATT – Punch Cards, 1992 January-March (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Dibner / CATT – Interface Architectural Signage, Inc., 1989 November-1992 May (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Union Gas (B.U.G.) Company, 1983 January-1984 September (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn Union Gas (B.U.G.) Company, 1978 January-1983 January (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Cush & Wake (Real Estate), 1983 June-1984 August (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising, 1986 October-1988 May (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising, 1984 December-1986 December (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Library Development, 1985 October-1986 December (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Library Development, 1984 May-1985 October (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Library Development, 1981 December-1984 March (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Metro Tech Center (M.T.C.) State Legislation – General, 1981 December-1982 March (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Originals – M.T.C., 1985 September-1988 November (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Originals – M.T.C., 1983 July-1986 March, Undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Dibner / CATT – General, 1987 January-December (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Dibner / CATT – General, 1988 January-December (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - M.T.C. – State Assistance – General - #1, 1981 January-1982 August (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - M.T.C. – State Assistance – General - #2, 1982 October-1983 April (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Dibner / CATT – Reports of Gift - Dibner Fund, 1984 January-1991 February (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Dibner / CATT – Reports of Gift, 1983 October-1989 December (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Dibner / CATT – Reports of Gift - Dibner Fund, 1979 August-1990 October (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans - CATV5, E101, 1989-1990? (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – AV 6-8, CATV 1-6, PA 1-3, 1989-1990? (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – P-100-501, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – E-401-502, SP-100-101, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – AV 6-8, CATV 1-6, PA 1-3, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – SK-MW 1-15, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – SK-MW 16-45, 1989-1990? (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A-100-107, 201-206, 211-212, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A-301-309, 311-316, 321-322, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A-331-333, 401-404, 411-412, 421-422, 431-433, 501-502, 511-513, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A-521, 551-554, 561-563, 581-582, 601-605, 801, 901-902, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – S-1-12, 101-105, 107, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – M-001, 101-106, 201, 301-302, 401-403, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Dibner / CATT - Floor Plans - M501-502, E001, E101-106, E301, L101-105, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – SK-MW 1-10, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – SK-MW 11-20, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – SK-MW 21-30, 1989-1990? (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – SK-MW 31-40, 1989-1990? (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – SK-MW 41-45, 1989-1990? (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A-561-563, 581-582, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A-601-605, 801, 901-902, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – S-1-8, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – S-9-12, 101-105, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – S-107, M-001, 101-106, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – M-201, 301-302, 401-403, 501-502, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – L-101-103, 105, P-001, 101-102, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – P-104-106, 301-303, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – P-401, 501, SP-001, 101, E-001, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – E-101-106, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – E-301, 401, 501-502, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A101A, 103A-B, 601A, 603A-B, November 1990 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A101-107, 201, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A202-206, 211-212, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A301-308, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A309, A311-316, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A321-322, 331-333, 401-403, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A404, 411-412, 421-422, 431-432, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A433, 501-502, 511-513, 521, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Dibner / CATT – Floor Plans – A551-554, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Dibner / CATT – Security System Specifications, 1990 January 15 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Dibner / CATT – Sheet Waterproofing, 1990 February 1 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Dibner / CATT – Section 2 – Table of Contents – 15501 Thru 15519, 1990 February 1 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Dibner / CATT – Section 4 – Division 17 – Table of Contents – 17100 Thru 17200, 1990 February 1 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Dibner / CATT – Section 1 – Division 15 – Mechanical, 1990 February 1 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Dibner / CATT – Division 16 – Electrical – 16010 Thru 16931, 1990 May 23 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Dibner / CATT – Architect's Summary of Audiovisual Basebuilding Requirements, 1989 December 19 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Dibner / CATT – Section Listing – Construction Specifications, 1990 February 1 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Dibner / CATT – Telecommunications Library – Architectural Standards, 1988 August-October (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Dibner / CATT – Telecommunications Library 1988 – Cable Standards, 1988 August (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Dibner / CATT – Invoices – Preconstruction, 1988 September-1989 August (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Dibner / CATT - Plan for CATT submitted to New York State Science & Technology Foundation - Part 1, 1993 September (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Dibner / CATT - Plan for CATT submitted to New York State Science & Technology Foundation - Part 2, 1993 September (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Dibner / CATT – Project Workbook 1, Preconstruction – 1989 – 1, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Dibner / CATT – Project Workbook 1, Preconstruction – 1989 – 2, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Dibner / CATT – Project Workbook 1, Preconstruction – 1989 – 3, 1989-1989 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Dibner / CATT – Project Workbook 1, Preconstruction – 1989 – 4, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Dibner / CATT – Project Workbook II – 1, 1988-1990 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Dibner / CATT – Project Workbook II – 2, 1991 February-October (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Dibner / CATT – Project Workbook II – 3 – Architects, 1989 December-1991 October (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Dibner / CATT – Project Workbook II – 4, 1990 February-November (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Dibner / CATT – Controlled Inspection Reports – 1, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Dibner / CATT – Controlled Inspection Reports – 2, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Dibner / CATT – Controlled Inspection Reports – 3, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Dibner / CATT – Controlled Inspection Reports – 4, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Dibner / CATT - 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Dibner / CATT – Physical Inventory, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Dibner / CATT – Library Equipment & Furnishings, Invoices, 1990-1992 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Dibner / CATT – Non-Building Costs, Invoices – 1, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Dibner / CATT – Non-Building Costs, Invoices – 2, 1990-1993 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #1 – 1, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #1 – 2, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #1 – 3, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #2 - 1, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #2 – 2, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #2 – 3, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #3 - 1, 1990-1992 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #3 - 2, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #3 - 3, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #4 – 1, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #4 -2, 1990-1992 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Dibner / CATT – Executed Subcontractors Agreement #4 -3, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Building – Design Development – 1, 1989 May-July (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Building – Design Development – 2, 1989 May 22 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Building – Design Development – 3, 1989 May 22 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Building – Addendum – 1, 1990 February (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Building – Addendum – 2, 1990 February (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Dibner Library / CATT Building – Addendum – 3, 1990 February (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Dibner / CATT - Oversize floor plans, 1988, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Dibner / CATT - Oversize floor plans, April 1990 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Series III: Polytechnic
  This series contains documents pertaining to George Bugliarello's administration as University President and includes correspondence, memoranda, pamphlets, and other promotional material highlighting George Bugliarello's administrative, development and fundraising efforts on behalf of Polytechnic.
  This series is arranged topically into 7 subseries.
  - Subseries A: Honorary Degrees, 1957-1986
    - Honorary Degrees, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Honorary Degrees - Gaertner, Dr. Wolfgang W., 1985 November (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Honorary Degrees - Nominations, 1980-1987 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Honorary Degrees - Nomination, Proposals, Undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Honorary Degrees - Educational Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Honorary Degrees - Miscellaneous, 1957-1979 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Honorary Degrees - Miscellaneous, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Honorary Degrees - Miscellaneous, 1982-1985 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Honorary Degrees - Miscellaneous, 1988, Undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Subseries B: SUNY Merger, 1965-1974
    - SUNY Merger – A-5, 1969 March - 1972 January (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - SUNY Merger – B (Budget), 1968-1972 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - SUNY Merger – C-1, 1968-1970 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - SUNY Merger – C-2, 1971 Fall (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - SUNY Merger – C-2 – 1, 1967-1970 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - SUNY Merger – C-2 – 2, 1966-1970 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - SUNY Merger – C-3 - 1, 1968-1970 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - SUNY Merger – C-3 - 2, 1968-1970 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - SUNY Merger – D 1 – 1, 1970-1972 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - SUNY Merger – D 1 – 2, 1971-1973 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - SUNY Merger – D 2 – 1, 1968-1974 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - SUNY Merger – D 2 – 2, 1969-1972 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - SUNY Merger – E, 1968-1970 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - SUNY Merger Contract, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - SUNY Merger Plans – Faculty 1, 1970-1971 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - SUNY Merger Plans – Faculty 2, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - SUNY Merger Plans – Faculty 3, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - SUNY Merger – Willenbroch Letter Index & Correspondence - 1, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - SUNY Merger – Willenbroch Letter Index & Correspondence - 2, 1965, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - SUNY Merger – Campus Master Program Guide for Facilities, Undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - SUNY Merger - Senator Bloom, 1968 May–1971 April (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - SUNY Merger – Miscellaneous, 1966-1972 January (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Subseries C: NYU-SES Merger
    - Notes and correspondence, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Meeting notes, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Reports, 1973-1976 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Clippings, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Subseries D: Education Committee of the Board of Trustees, 1970-1983
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1970-1971 February (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1971 December-1974 August (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1974 October-December (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1982 July-1983 February (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1983 January-March (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1983 March-December (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Education Committee of the Board, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Subseries E: Polytechnic Corporation Committees, 1981-1993
    - Education Committee of the Corporation, 1984 May-1985 November (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Education Committee of the Corporation – Minutes, Agenda, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Education Committee of the Corporation – Long-term Neighborhood Plan, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Education Committee of the Corporation – Honorary Degrees, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Education Committee of the Corporation, 1986 May-November (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Education Committee of the Corporation, 1986 December-1987 January (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Education Committee of the Corporation, 1987 February-March (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Education Committee of the Corporation, 1987 May-1988 April (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Education Committee of the Corporation, Undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Polytechnic University - Finance Committee, 1986 May-1987 April (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Polytechnic University – Departmental Overviews, 1986 April-1987 April (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Polytechnic University – Departments, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Engineering Self-Study, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Polytechnic University – Bylaws, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Polytechnic University – Corporation – 3 Year Budget Projection, 1983 December-1984 November (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Polytechnic University – Ad Hoc Evaluations For Institute Professorship Nominees, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Polytechnic University – Corporation Committees, 1983-1985 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Polytechnic University – Resolution of the Corporation, 1986 March (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Polytechnic University – Published Speeches, 1979-1993 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Subseries F: Board Meeting Minutes, 1984-1987
    - Executive Committee Meeting - September 1, 1986, 1986 March-October (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Polytechnic University – Campaign Report, 1986 October 21 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Polytechnic University – Executive Committee, 1986 May-June (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Polytechnic University – Meeting of the Corporation, 1984 August-1986 June (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Polytechnic University – Executive Committee Meeting, 1986 February-July (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Polytechnic University – Administrative – Miscellaneous, 1986 March-July (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Polytechnic University – Corporation Meetings – Hotel Reservation, 1985 August-1986 April (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Polytechnic University – Executive Committee Meeting, 1985 December 5 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Polytechnic University – Executive Committee Meeting, 1985 October 15 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Polytechnic University – Executive Committee Meeting, 1985 September 12 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Polytechnic University - Corporation Meeting, 1986 January 16 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Polytechnic University – Corporation Meeting, 1985 January 17 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Polytechnic University – Board Retreat, 1986 April-November (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Polytechnic University – Corporation Retreat Response Forms, October-November 1986, 1986 July-November (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Polytechnic University – Corporation Meetings – Miscellaneous, 1984 November-1986 March (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Polytechnic University – Corporation Meetings – Miscellaneous, 1986 April-May, Undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Polytechnic University – President's Report Master List, 1986 June-1987 June (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Polytechnic University - Executive Committee Meeting, February 14, 1985, 1984 November-1985 February (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Subseries G: Board Members, 1968-1990